# Paulina Wdowicz

**Environmental Protection Specialist** 

paulina.wdowicz₁@gmail.com

**L** 534-068-439

https://github.com/PaulinaWdowicz

www.linkedin.com/in/paulina-wdowicz

#### About me

During my engineering studies at Warsaw University of Technology, I was a part of WUT Students' Council, where I got invaluable experience in student project planning and execution. Since graduation, I have worked in the field of waste management in the two largest waste management companies in Warsaw. My position required me to be precise, to pay attention to details and to meet deadlines.

For the last months I have been developing my skills in the area of manual testing of IT products. I would like to use my personal qualities and past experience in new challenging QA projects.

## Knowledge

Language | English intermediate level (B2 certificate)

Polish native

Programming Python basic level

languages | **SQL** basic level

Technical skills | Jira basic level | Mantis basic level | TestRail basic level

## Courses and trainings

- Fundamentals of Software Testing QATestLab
- · Manual Software Testing Basics Udemy
- Jira Beginners Course Project Management Udemy
- Introduction to SQL: Data Management and Querying Khan Academy

### **Education**

Warsaw University of Technology, Faculty of Building Services, Hydro and Environmental Engineering Environmental Protection course - Bachelor (BSc.) + Master (MSc.) degree

Experience

07.2022-now | "BYŚ" Wojciech Byśkiniewicz Environmental protection and service specialist
01.2019 - 06.2022 | Miejskie Przedsiębiorstwo Oczyszczania Sp.z o.o. w m. st. Warszawie

Municipal waste incineration plant (ZOG) Waste management specialist

01.2015-01.2019 | The Warsaw University of Technology Students' Council

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).